qantascash.com 2019-09-02

# QANTAS MONEY PRIVACY STATEMENT

QANTAS MONEY PRIVACY STATEMENT
1. Introduction
   This Qantas Money Privacy Statement explains how Qantas* collects, holds, uses and discloses your
   personal information under the Australian Privacy Principles when you use the Qantas Money app and
   website.
   This Qantas Money Privacy Statement supplements the Qantas Privacy Statement. The Qantas Privacy
   Statement should be read in conjunction with this statement.
2. Information we collect
   When you use the Qantas Money app and website, we may also collect:
        ° information you supply in relation to applying for any products offered on the Qantas Money app
           or website;
        ° your account credentials (including the Primary Account Number of your card);
        ° your account information; and
        ° transaction details,
   in respect of any account which you link to the Qantas Money app and website.
   This information may be collected from you directly, from the financial institution that provide your
   nominated accounts to you, or from third parties providing services to us (such as financial institutions).
   If the date of birth and/or mother’s maiden name provided in your application do not match the
   information stored in your Qantas Frequent Flyer profile, and if your application is approved, we will
   update the date of birth and/or mother’s maiden name in your Qantas Frequent Flyer profile with the
   information you provided during your application.
3. How we use your personal information
   We use this information for the purpose of:
        ° aggregating information about your transactions by using account data from financial
           institutions on your behalf;
        ° providing you with access to personal financial management features. These features include the
           ability to categorise transactions, visualise your spend by category and time period, and set
           budgets;

        ° provide you with personalised offers to enable you to earn loyalty points based on your spend or
           behaviour with participating merchants; and
        ° providing you with enhanced benefits and services by understanding and analysing your interests
           and hobbies.
   If we do not collect your personal information, we will not be able to provide you with these services.
4. Disclosure of personal information
   This information may be disclosed to third party service providers to perform the transaction
   aggregation services. The information will be encrypted and cached by them and securely stored by us.
   We may also provide your transaction history to service providers to enable personalised offer
   matching, assignment and fulfilment based on your previous spend. This also allows us to verify
   whether or not you have fulfilled the terms of a specific personalised offer.
   We may also disclose your personal information to other service providers including those providing
   billing services, data analytics services and software as a service products which are incorporated into
   the Qantas Money app and website.
5. Further information
   Please refer to the Qantas Privacy Statement for further information on how Qantas handles your
   personal information.
   The Qantas Privacy Statement includes information about:
        ° how you may access and correct personal information we hold about you; and
        ° how you may make a privacy complaint and how Qantas will deal with any complaint.
6. Disclosure to overseas recipients
   We may also disclose your personal information to data processors (including operators of global travel
   distribution systems), customer service providers and managers of our financial products located
   overseas. The countries in which these third parties are located include the United Kingdom, the United
   States and Germany.
7. Our contact details
   You can contact us by completing the form located at:
   qantas.com/privacyquestions

or by writing to:
Qantas Customer Care
Qantas Airways Limited
10 Bourke Road
Mascot NSW 2020
Australia
* Qantas means Qantas Airways Limited and its related bodies corporate, excluding companies in the
Jetstar Group**, Wishlist Holdings Limited and Qantas Superannuation Limited.
** Jetstar Group means Jetstar Airways Pty Ltd and its subsidiaries, and all Jetstar branded entities.
